Ah
Google Pixel Presents
Another Sky
Tonight's guest is Erika Ikuta
Nice to meet you
Erika, how old are you?
I'm 29
29?
Yes
You have a long history as an entertainer
Since I was 15
Since you were 15?
Yes
It's been 6 years since I've graduated
It's been 6 years
It's been about 4 years
That's a long time
What happened in the last 2 years?
You must have graduated already
So sharp
I can see the snow
I've never seen snow like this before
Here we are
It's snowing
Dusseldorf is a city where I was born and raised until I was 5 years old
Do you remember?
I can't see the view
It's all white
It's amazing
Dusseldorf is located on the east coast of Reinger
There are many Japanese-style companies
It's the city where the most Japanese live in Germany
Ikuta was born and raised in the middle school and lived until he was 5 years old
10 years ago, when I was in my last 10s, I came to Germany to study photography
This is my last 20s
It's amazing
This is the street where I used to live
I've never seen snow like this before
Can you see it?
Here?
No
It's a five-person house
There were a few people living together
The garden is the same
I liked singing since I was little
I imitated my mom's singing
I made it and sang it
I took a picture with my sister when I was little
Where did I take it?
Here it is
The store
A photo book
A photo book from Germany 10 years ago
Here it is
You took it at home?
Yes
I was 19 years old when I was in my last 10s
I think I was about 4 years old
I didn't expect to come to Germany again at the end of my 20s
Amazing
It's a completely different season
It's amazing
I can't stop it
I want to take it every time
She met her life partner in Germany
There is a classroom where I started learning piano
My sister started learning piano first
You started learning piano in Germany?
I wanted to imitate everything my sister was doing
If my sister did it, I would do it too
Here it is
Koyama Piano Classroom
I've been playing the piano for the first time in 24 years since I was 5 years old
I'm nervous
It's cute
She's playing the piano
It's been a long time
You haven't changed at all
I've always been cute
You've changed
I'm so happy
It's been a long time
Koyama Piano Classroom
It was her first time playing the piano
Erika was training for the sound
I had to play the sound and play it every day
My mom used to give me flags and lessons
But now I can play it
That's good
Do you want to see the sheet music you used to play?
I want to see it
I used to play it
My mom sent me a picture from home
My teacher made it by hand
I think it was fun
She drew it in this way
I think it was fun because she taught me this way
For the first time, the dots are connected
This is Erika
The moon is shining
The picture is still in this quality
She started to play
It's snowing
It's true
What?
Amazing
I didn't know there was such an era
Of course, You don't remember it
I met myself in the past
Through this era
I'm going to grow up
That's right
I was a child
I think it was something I couldn't do only with my own will
To my teacher and my mother
I think I got a real gift of life
The most important thing in a child's talent
And there is something that the teacher can't teach
The love for music
No matter how hard the teacher works
I can't stick to the child
I think Erika had it
That's why I was able to practice
I think I like music
I like it and I want to do it
I've been doing it since I was a child
Everything was connected to this sky
I remember it was fun even though I was doing it
That's right
I remember it was fun
After all, the teacher and my mother were very enthusiastic
I think that's why I was able to continue
There is Germany that you can enjoy only when you become an adult
I want to drink beer
Last time I was 19 years old
I couldn't drink it yet
So on this trip
Let's have a real beer
The bronze-colored beer is the local specialty
Thank you for joining us on this trip to Germany
Cheers
I like it
It's delicious
It's a lot
Let's share it with everyone
Amazing
I don't know how to eat
The power
Thank you
It's very delicious
The meat is very soft
It's very smooth
She came to Japan at the age of 5
She found the way to go
When I was about 6 years old
I was taken by my musical brother
The stage was full of singing, dancing, acting, and music
I thought I was doing everything I wanted to do
I was attracted immediately
I auditioned
I was completely down
The beginning of the theater is the age of the high school incident
I've been playing the piano since I was 5 years old
My father told me that the world of classical music is not easy
I should think about it well
I thought about the progress of the exam
I said I wanted to do it while crying
He bought me a grand piano
It's a classic piano that aims to go to music school
Everyone practices with a grand piano
I broke my father's room
I put in a room
I auditioned for an idol without knowing it
During the summer vacation
I didn't know
I happen to see the audition information of Nogizaka
I want to sing and dance on stage
The host is Sony Music
Did you see that?
The host is Sony Music?
Your father is amazing
He did his own audition
The world of classical music
She said she wanted to do it while crying
You became an idol
I closed the door and said, why?
Your father said
You were in the audition room
Your family didn't know
I was studying for the exam
I became an idol after audition
I had two different paths
It's totally different from classical music
I practiced hard
I took the exam
I did it well
If I failed the exam, I couldn't face it
Even though you did it
The two-stage waraji was not easy
I have a best friend
She's been with me since I was in elementary school
She's always with me
I talk to my friends
I use too much energy
I'm like a peasant
I have a strong resolve
Even if I don't have enough power
I want to be strong
I want to connect
The two paths of piano and idol
At last
Because I can play the piano
They let me sing
It's the first time I've used piano
It's been connected to me
At that time, I thought I chose another option
It wasn't a mistake
I suddenly remembered
The first reason why I chose the path of entertainment
You said you wanted to do musicals
When I was about 19
I saw the music video
I wanted to do it
But I couldn't afford it
The piano and the idol were out of control
I wanted to do musicals
I thought I had to quit the group
I went to talk to the staff
They told me I could do it while I was there
So
I auditioned
You auditioned?
Yes
It was very difficult
I had to take a step
I wanted to take the responsibility
So I tried my best
I was ready
I took the responsibility
I kept doing it
I grew so much that I couldn't believe it
It must be hard for people around you
I think so
You must be running
I think about it now
I can't take the step
I'm still in my teens
I wanted to do it
But I couldn't
That's why I'm here
Another Sky
Let's expand your journey
It's on Google Pixel
Nostalgia and love
We go to the next town
It's beautiful
It's cool
Is this the Berlin Cathedral?
Amazing
It's a beautiful view
It's the first time I have come to Berlin
I wanted to go there one day
City Berlin
It was a long time ago that a sad wall broke through the city
Now
Art
Artist
Walking around the city
I heard that it's rare to walk in Berlin
Please tell me the recommended shopping spots in Berlin
If you want to buy souvenirs,
I want to go to the Ampelmann shop with the German signal mark
I want to go to the Hakkeshi Heifei
I want to buy souvenirs and buy souvenirs
After the snow, they go shopping
Stars are falling
Here
Snow is falling
Look at this
I can see it
It's the easiest way to remove your hair
It's in the shape of a snowman
Can you see it?
Amazing
Is there really snow?
It's amazing
I'm so excited
It's a beautiful city
Amazing
It's fashionable
Is this the courtyard?
It's a combination of the eight courtyards
I want to give it to my friends
I want to give it to myself
It's cute
That's it
It's a signal marker
It's cute
Hello
Ampelmann
The character is used in the Berlin signal marker
It takes a lot of time to decide
What should I do?
It's for humans
From the way they shop, they can see unexpected faces
It's cute
What is this?
I wonder what this is
It's so bad
What is this?
It's used so much abroad
Amazing
What is this?
It's used
I can see something
What is this?
I said it again
It's amazing
What is this?
It's used so much
No one is here
It was a strange answer
It's cute
It's written on the Berlin wall
I don't know
I'm so excited because I'm at the site
It's a souvenir
It's a Berlin wall
Thank you
I bought it!
I bought a souvenir for you two
Did you buy that?
I bought it
It's a Berlin wall Ampelmann
It was destroyed in 1989
You should go to Yoshimoto
Really?
Amazing
At night, they went to a place they wanted to visit
We went to Friedrich Stadtpalast
Amazing
It's rare to see such a big theater in Japan
How is it?
Even the photos are amazing
It was amazing
It was a great stage
Dancing to the song and mixing the music
They are impressed by the review
But there is a surprise
It's not like that
I was told not to film inside when they play
But there is no one in the stage before the opening
They said you can film
It's a great theater
It's amazing
Welcome to your palace
Berlin's No.1 with the biggest theater in the world
They are challenging me
I don't know what they are saying
They enjoyed the impression of Berlin
It's amazing
The temperature is amazing
It's full of the ultimate of entertainment
There are songs, dances, live performances
Circus-like acrobatic
I wonder if it will be transmitted
As a person who is allowed to stand on the stage
I don't want to forget this feeling
Today is the infinite stage
It's been a long time since I went up
It's amazing
I was convinced of the infinite power of entertainment
With this, I can fly higher
When I was in the group, I was mainly in the group
I did a lot of musicals
So when I stood alone
While taking care of the musical
I want to try other fields
I stepped on the scene of the video
Radio or mc
I haven't done it at all
That's a great path
I think it's spreading new
Is this your own voice?
Is this a concert tour?
I have lived while expressing
There are important people I met there
They are looking forward to it
I want to do what I can do
I want to do only what I can do
Input and output
20 units piled up
How can 30 units proceed?
Can you play something?
In front of the teacher
Where is Erika Ikuta going?
Can you play something?
In front of the teacher
I want you to play something
I was nervous
What is this?
Dynamic
It's dynamic
I feel a little young
I am 10m away from it
I'm looking at it
I'm starting too much
I'm having a lesson
I want you to play something
Like that
I think that's good
It's not just the piano
I may need it for everything
Erika is a very hard-working child
I want to live like that in my 30s
I want to have a delicate calm
Piano and real life are not enough
I want to do my best
Piano does not lie
Even if you look calm, your life is ahead
I have been doing it with momentum and will power
I think that calmness is the task of my life
Beethoven played today
Beethoven played 5 years later
Beethoven played 10 years later
I think it will change
I want to grow with music
The music that plays from time to time
It will be a sign of life
Let's step forward without fear of change
To an unlimited world
This is my Another Sky
Germany
Thank you
Another Sky is your journey
I sent it with Google Pixel
This week
I think it was a journey that was a little different from my own
The official X program is being broadcast
Photos that can only be seen here
Follow and repost
Please
Thank you
If you want to see it again
Tver Furu